ps3trophies.org 2017-09-01

# PlaystationTrophies.org - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy for PlaystationTrophies.org 

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at **feedback [at] ps3t.org**. 

At PlaystationTrophies.org, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by PlaystationTrophies.org and how it is used. 

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, PlaystationTrophies.org makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Analytics**  
We’ve implemented Google Analytics based on Display Advertising (e.g. Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting).

We and third-party vendors, including Google, will use this remarking information and data based on previous visits to our site to serve relevant messages across the web.

You can opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting Google's [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads). 

Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

 **3rd party cookies**  
We uses cookies on our websites in order to provide enhanced functionality to users, such as user accounts and saved preferences. We also use cookies to ensure that you see the most relevant ads and limit the number of times we show you the same advertisements.

If you continue to use this site, we'll assume you are happy to accept these cookies. Some of the adverts carried on our websites are delivered by third party servers and in doing so they may leave cookies on your machine.

You may opt-out of these cookies by following these links:  
MediaMind opt-out: <http://ds.serving-sys.com/OBA/Europe/Opt-out.aspx>  
FlashTalking opt-out: <http://www.flashtalking.com/cookieOptOut.html>  
MindShare opt-out: <http://www.mindshareworld.com/privacy>
